{
    "1628331351672778754": {
        "attachments": {
            "media_keys": [
                "7_1628329467826380800"
            ]
        },
        "author_id": "380801406",
        "created_at": "2023-02-22T09:50:21.000Z",
        "edit_history_tweet_ids": [
            "1628331351672778754"
        ],
        "entities": {
            "annotations": [
                {
                    "end": 25,
                    "normalized_text": "Bolivia",
                    "probability": 0.968,
                    "start": 19,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 33,
                    "normalized_text": "Peru",
                    "probability": 0.9779,
                    "start": 30,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 50,
                    "normalized_text": "Julian Pueschel",
                    "probability": 0.6946,
                    "start": 36,
                    "type": "Person"
                },
                {
                    "end": 64,
                    "normalized_text": "Pan America",
                    "probability": 0.7147,
                    "start": 54,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 163,
                    "normalized_text": "Peru",
                    "probability": 0.9761,
                    "start": 160,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 223,
                    "normalized_text": "lake",
                    "probability": 0.452,
                    "start": 220,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 232,
                    "normalized_text": "Titicaca",
                    "probability": 0.773,
                    "start": 225,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 278,
                    "normalized_text": "Maersk",
                    "probability": 0.5791,
                    "start": 273,
                    "type": "Place"
                }
            ],
            "hashtags": [
                {
                    "end": 85,
                    "start": 77,
                    "tag": "journey"
                },
                {
                    "end": 190,
                    "start": 180,
                    "tag": "community"
                },
                {
                    "end": 216,
                    "start": 208,
                    "tag": "culture"
                },
                {
                    "end": 279,
                    "start": 272,
                    "tag": "Maersk"
                }
            ],
            "urls": [
                {
                    "display_url": "youtu.be/F23AqmxHKeY",
                    "end": 270,
                    "expanded_url": "https://youtu.be/F23AqmxHKeY",
                    "start": 247,
                    "url": "https://t.co/rFZUA4qT5k"
                },
                {
                    "display_url": "pic.twitter.com/Q2FJ8zlTEN",
                    "end": 303,
                    "expanded_url": "https://twitter.com/Maersk/status/1628331351672778754/video/1",
                    "media_key": "7_1628329467826380800",
                    "start": 280,
                    "url": "https://t.co/Q2FJ8zlTEN"
                }
            ]
        },
        "id": "1628331351672778754",
        "lang": "en",
        "public_metrics": {
            "bookmark_count": 0,
            "impression_count": 4038,
            "like_count": 39,
            "quote_count": 0,
            "reply_count": 2,
            "retweet_count": 9
        },
        "text": "🏍Riding into Ep 2: Bolivia to Peru. Julian Pueschel’s Pan America motorcycle #journey continues with a pit stop at the world’s largest salt flat and onwards to Peru to stay with a #community preserving their #culture on lake Titicaca. Watch here: https://t.co/rFZUA4qT5k\n\n#Maersk https://t.co/Q2FJ8zlTEN"
    }
}