{
    "1646826160808919040": {
        "attachments": {
            "media_keys": [
                "7_1646825412637470720"
            ]
        },
        "author_id": "380801406",
        "created_at": "2023-04-14T10:42:07.000Z",
        "edit_history_tweet_ids": [
            "1646826160808919040"
        ],
        "entities": {
            "annotations": [
                {
                    "end": 27,
                    "normalized_text": "o Nikolaj Myh",
                    "probability": 0.7441,
                    "start": 15,
                    "type": "Person"
                },
                {
                    "end": 66,
                    "normalized_text": "d Boei",
                    "probability": 0.5871,
                    "start": 61,
                    "type": "Organization"
                },
                {
                    "end": 101,
                    "normalized_text": "n Billu",
                    "probability": 0.7569,
                    "start": 95,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 113,
                    "normalized_text": ", Copenhag",
                    "probability": 0.9823,
                    "start": 104,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 126,
                    "normalized_text": "d Hangzh",
                    "probability": 0.9783,
                    "start": 119,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 133,
                    "normalized_text": ", Chi",
                    "probability": 0.9839,
                    "start": 129,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 183,
                    "normalized_text": " #MaerskAirCar",
                    "probability": 0.6864,
                    "start": 170,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 209,
                    "normalized_text": "m Euro",
                    "probability": 0.9426,
                    "start": 204,
                    "type": "Place"
                }
            ],
            "hashtags": [
                {
                    "end": 38,
                    "start": 32,
                    "tag": "Pilot"
                },
                {
                    "end": 186,
                    "start": 171,
                    "tag": "MaerskAirCargo"
                },
                {
                    "end": 200,
                    "start": 194,
                    "tag": "cargo"
                }
            ],
            "urls": [
                {
                    "display_url": "lnkd.in/ed8pwYeS",
                    "end": 280,
                    "expanded_url": "https://lnkd.in/ed8pwYeS",
                    "start": 257,
                    "unwound_url": "https://www.maersk.com/news/articles/2023/04/12/maersk-air-cargo-billund-hub?exit=Newsletter",
                    "url": "https://t.co/NnpJBnzJkH"
                },
                {
                    "display_url": "pic.twitter.com/UxzLRxq1zZ",
                    "end": 304,
                    "expanded_url": "https://twitter.com/Maersk/status/1646826160808919040/video/1",
                    "media_key": "7_1646825412637470720",
                    "start": 281,
                    "url": "https://t.co/UxzLRxq1zZ"
                }
            ]
        },
        "id": "1646826160808919040",
        "lang": "en",
        "public_metrics": {
            "bookmark_count": 0,
            "impression_count": 14092,
            "like_count": 75,
            "quote_count": 2,
            "reply_count": 1,
            "retweet_count": 10
        },
        "text": "🧑🏽‍✈️We spoke to Nikolaj Myhre, #Pilot to our newly \nconverted Boeing 767-300 freighters between Billund, Copenhagen and Hangzhou, China - what it takes to be a pilot for #MaerskAirCargo moving #cargo from Europe to Asia🌍\n \n👉Read more about the route here: https://t.co/NnpJBnzJkH https://t.co/UxzLRxq1zZ"
    }
}