{
    "1658816571513470978": {
        "attachments": {
            "media_keys": [
                "3_1658816525740961793"
            ]
        },
        "author_id": "380801406",
        "created_at": "2023-05-17T12:47:44.000Z",
        "edit_history_tweet_ids": [
            "1658816571513470978"
        ],
        "entities": {
            "annotations": [
                {
                    "end": 43,
                    "normalized_text": "Middle East",
                    "probability": 0.7122,
                    "start": 33,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 54,
                    "normalized_text": "Europe",
                    "probability": 0.9565,
                    "start": 49,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 101,
                    "normalized_text": "Al Maha",
                    "probability": 0.4908,
                    "start": 95,
                    "type": "Person"
                },
                {
                    "end": 157,
                    "normalized_text": "UAE",
                    "probability": 0.9848,
                    "start": 155,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 171,
                    "normalized_text": "Saudi Arabia",
                    "probability": 0.986,
                    "start": 160,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 177,
                    "normalized_text": "Oman",
                    "probability": 0.9863,
                    "start": 174,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 184,
                    "normalized_text": "Qatar",
                    "probability": 0.9839,
                    "start": 180,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 191,
                    "normalized_text": "Egypt",
                    "probability": 0.9886,
                    "start": 187,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 258,
                    "normalized_text": "Maersk",
                    "probability": 0.8313,
                    "start": 253,
                    "type": "Place"
                }
            ],
            "hashtags": [
                {
                    "end": 259,
                    "start": 252,
                    "tag": "Maersk"
                },
                {
                    "end": 272,
                    "start": 260,
                    "tag": "supplychain"
                }
            ],
            "urls": [
                {
                    "display_url": "lnkd.in/eGZVP4n9",
                    "end": 249,
                    "expanded_url": "https://lnkd.in/eGZVP4n9",
                    "start": 226,
                    "status": 200,
                    "unwound_url": "https://www.maersk.com/news/articles/2023/05/17/maersk-announces-ai-maha-ocean-service-connecting-the-middle-east-and-west-africa-markets",
                    "url": "https://t.co/yWoSv3ssYf"
                },
                {
                    "display_url": "pic.twitter.com/7gGCCL1AGs",
                    "end": 296,
                    "expanded_url": "https://twitter.com/Maersk/status/1658816571513470978/photo/1",
                    "media_key": "3_1658816525740961793",
                    "start": 273,
                    "url": "https://t.co/7gGCCL1AGs"
                }
            ]
        },
        "id": "1658816571513470978",
        "lang": "en",
        "public_metrics": {
            "bookmark_count": 0,
            "impression_count": 9243,
            "like_count": 91,
            "quote_count": 2,
            "reply_count": 5,
            "retweet_count": 16
        },
        "text": "New ocean service connecting the Middle East and Europe markets🚢 The newly introduced service, Al Maha, will rotate between the important ports across the UAE, Saudi Arabia, Oman, Qatar, Egypt, and Morocco📷Read press release: https://t.co/yWoSv3ssYf \n\n#Maersk #supplychain https://t.co/7gGCCL1AGs"
    }
}