{
    "1675806591684333568": {
        "attachments": {
            "media_keys": [
                "7_1675770230507810816"
            ]
        },
        "author_id": "380801406",
        "created_at": "2023-07-03T10:00:01.000Z",
        "edit_history_tweet_ids": [
            "1675806591684333568"
        ],
        "entities": {
            "annotations": [
                {
                    "end": 25,
                    "normalized_text": "DTU",
                    "probability": 0.7829,
                    "start": 23,
                    "type": "Organization"
                },
                {
                    "end": 59,
                    "normalized_text": "Technical University of Denmark",
                    "probability": 0.801,
                    "start": 29,
                    "type": "Organization"
                },
                {
                    "end": 89,
                    "normalized_text": "Maersk",
                    "probability": 0.7064,
                    "start": 84,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 105,
                    "normalized_text": "Gothenburg",
                    "probability": 0.7555,
                    "start": 96,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 113,
                    "normalized_text": "Sweden",
                    "probability": 0.91,
                    "start": 108,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 130,
                    "normalized_text": "Wilhelmshaven",
                    "probability": 0.7308,
                    "start": 118,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 139,
                    "normalized_text": "Germany",
                    "probability": 0.9186,
                    "start": 133,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 215,
                    "normalized_text": "Lars Hansmann",
                    "probability": 0.5019,
                    "start": 203,
                    "type": "Other"
                },
                {
                    "end": 238,
                    "normalized_text": "DTU",
                    "probability": 0.6572,
                    "start": 236,
                    "type": "Organization"
                }
            ],
            "hashtags": [
                {
                    "end": 90,
                    "start": 83,
                    "tag": "Maersk"
                }
            ],
            "urls": [
                {
                    "display_url": "pic.twitter.com/NuGExaaXoq",
                    "end": 294,
                    "expanded_url": "https://twitter.com/Maersk/status/1675806591684333568/video/1",
                    "media_key": "7_1675770230507810816",
                    "start": 271,
                    "url": "https://t.co/NuGExaaXoq"
                }
            ]
        },
        "id": "1675806591684333568",
        "lang": "en",
        "public_metrics": {
            "bookmark_count": 0,
            "impression_count": 3284,
            "like_count": 32,
            "quote_count": 0,
            "reply_count": 0,
            "retweet_count": 6
        },
        "text": "Recently students from DTU - Technical University of Denmark sailed onboard Munich #Maersk from Gothenburg, Sweden to Wilhelmshaven, Germany learning about our vessels and how we operate them. Hear from Lars Hansmann, Master Student at DTU, how he experienced the sail👇🏼 https://t.co/NuGExaaXoq"
    }
}