{
    "1526986476013207552": {
        "attachments": {
            "media_keys": [
                "3_1526986460762603522",
                "3_1526986464361336835",
                "3_1526986468572405760",
                "3_1526986472922009601"
            ]
        },
        "author_id": "156646851",
        "created_at": "2022-05-18T18:02:00.000Z",
        "edit_history_tweet_ids": [
            "1526986476013207552"
        ],
        "entities": {
            "annotations": [
                {
                    "end": 13,
                    "normalized_text": "Vestas",
                    "probability": 0.8447,
                    "start": 8,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 58,
                    "normalized_text": "NorthSeaSummit",
                    "probability": 0.418,
                    "start": 45,
                    "type": "Other"
                },
                {
                    "end": 95,
                    "normalized_text": "Esbjerg",
                    "probability": 0.9707,
                    "start": 89,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 104,
                    "normalized_text": "Denmark",
                    "probability": 0.9875,
                    "start": 98,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 132,
                    "normalized_text": "Germany",
                    "probability": 0.9691,
                    "start": 126,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 145,
                    "normalized_text": "Netherlands",
                    "probability": 0.9856,
                    "start": 135,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 154,
                    "normalized_text": "Belgium",
                    "probability": 0.9831,
                    "start": 148,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 163,
                    "normalized_text": "Denmark",
                    "probability": 0.9878,
                    "start": 157,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 192,
                    "normalized_text": "European Commission",
                    "probability": 0.8102,
                    "start": 174,
                    "type": "Organization"
                },
                {
                    "end": 268,
                    "normalized_text": "North Sea",
                    "probability": 0.7762,
                    "start": 260,
                    "type": "Place"
                }
            ],
            "hashtags": [
                {
                    "end": 14,
                    "start": 7,
                    "tag": "Vestas"
                },
                {
                    "end": 59,
                    "start": 44,
                    "tag": "NorthSeaSummit"
                },
                {
                    "end": 96,
                    "start": 88,
                    "tag": "Esbjerg"
                },
                {
                    "end": 243,
                    "start": 230,
                    "tag": "offshorewind"
                }
            ],
            "urls": [
                {
                    "display_url": "pic.twitter.com/xbnTryE8IJ",
                    "end": 302,
                    "expanded_url": "https://twitter.com/Vestas/status/1526986476013207552/photo/1",
                    "media_key": "3_1526986460762603522",
                    "start": 279,
                    "url": "https://t.co/xbnTryE8IJ"
                },
                {
                    "display_url": "pic.twitter.com/xbnTryE8IJ",
                    "end": 302,
                    "expanded_url": "https://twitter.com/Vestas/status/1526986476013207552/photo/1",
                    "media_key": "3_1526986464361336835",
                    "start": 279,
                    "url": "https://t.co/xbnTryE8IJ"
                },
                {
                    "display_url": "pic.twitter.com/xbnTryE8IJ",
                    "end": 302,
                    "expanded_url": "https://twitter.com/Vestas/status/1526986476013207552/photo/1",
                    "media_key": "3_1526986468572405760",
                    "start": 279,
                    "url": "https://t.co/xbnTryE8IJ"
                },
                {
                    "display_url": "pic.twitter.com/xbnTryE8IJ",
                    "end": 302,
                    "expanded_url": "https://twitter.com/Vestas/status/1526986476013207552/photo/1",
                    "media_key": "3_1526986472922009601",
                    "start": 279,
                    "url": "https://t.co/xbnTryE8IJ"
                }
            ]
        },
        "id": "1526986476013207552",
        "lang": "en",
        "public_metrics": {
            "bookmark_count": 0,
            "impression_count": 0,
            "like_count": 58,
            "quote_count": 1,
            "reply_count": 2,
            "retweet_count": 5
        },
        "text": "Today, #Vestas had the pleasure to host the #NorthSeaSummit at our offshore facility in #Esbjerg, Denmark, where leaders from Germany, Netherlands, Belgium, Denmark, and the European Commission pledged to build at least 150 GW of #offshorewind capacity in the North Sea by 2050. https://t.co/xbnTryE8IJ"
    }
}