{
    "1526925260796440582": {
        "attachments": {
            "media_keys": [
                "3_1526925259009576964"
            ]
        },
        "author_id": "156646851",
        "created_at": "2022-05-18T13:58:45.000Z",
        "edit_history_tweet_ids": [
            "1526925260796440582"
        ],
        "entities": {
            "annotations": [
                {
                    "end": 5,
                    "normalized_text": "Vestas",
                    "probability": 0.7719,
                    "start": 0,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 40,
                    "normalized_text": "NorthSeaSummit",
                    "probability": 0.4309,
                    "start": 27,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 72,
                    "normalized_text": "Germany",
                    "probability": 0.9595,
                    "start": 66,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 89,
                    "normalized_text": "Netherlands",
                    "probability": 0.9555,
                    "start": 79,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 98,
                    "normalized_text": "Belgium",
                    "probability": 0.9767,
                    "start": 92,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 107,
                    "normalized_text": "Denmark",
                    "probability": 0.98,
                    "start": 101,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 136,
                    "normalized_text": "European Commission",
                    "probability": 0.7976,
                    "start": 118,
                    "type": "Organization"
                },
                {
                    "end": 233,
                    "normalized_text": "Esbjerg",
                    "probability": 0.9273,
                    "start": 227,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 242,
                    "normalized_text": "Denmark",
                    "probability": 0.9725,
                    "start": 236,
                    "type": "Place"
                }
            ],
            "hashtags": [
                {
                    "end": 41,
                    "start": 26,
                    "tag": "NorthSeaSummit"
                },
                {
                    "end": 234,
                    "start": 226,
                    "tag": "Esbjerg"
                }
            ],
            "urls": [
                {
                    "display_url": "pic.twitter.com/iAH7XxWKhh",
                    "end": 271,
                    "expanded_url": "https://twitter.com/Vestas/status/1526925260796440582/photo/1",
                    "media_key": "3_1526925259009576964",
                    "start": 248,
                    "url": "https://t.co/iAH7XxWKhh"
                }
            ]
        },
        "id": "1526925260796440582",
        "lang": "en",
        "public_metrics": {
            "bookmark_count": 0,
            "impression_count": 0,
            "like_count": 43,
            "quote_count": 1,
            "reply_count": 0,
            "retweet_count": 5
        },
        "text": "Vestas is hosting today’s #NorthSeaSummit, welcoming leaders from Germany, the Netherlands, Belgium, Denmark, and the European Commission as well as key players from the European wind industry at our offshore wind facility in #Esbjerg, Denmark 🇩🇰. https://t.co/iAH7XxWKhh"
    }
}