{
    "1717186761242337787": {
        "attachments": {
            "media_keys": [
                "3_1717186755936309249"
            ]
        },
        "author_id": "393757140",
        "created_at": "2023-10-25T14:30:02.000Z",
        "edit_history_tweet_ids": [
            "1717186761242337787"
        ],
        "entities": {
            "annotations": [
                {
                    "end": 3,
                    "normalized_text": "Asia",
                    "probability": 0.9775,
                    "start": 0,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 41,
                    "normalized_text": "ClimateChange",
                    "probability": 0.7903,
                    "start": 29,
                    "type": "Other"
                },
                {
                    "end": 53,
                    "normalized_text": "India",
                    "probability": 0.9764,
                    "start": 49,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 60,
                    "normalized_text": "China",
                    "probability": 0.9873,
                    "start": 56,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 75,
                    "normalized_text": "Singapore",
                    "probability": 0.9779,
                    "start": 67,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 160,
                    "normalized_text": "Nikkei",
                    "probability": 0.5585,
                    "start": 155,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 165,
                    "normalized_text": "Asia",
                    "probability": 0.3074,
                    "start": 162,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 174,
                    "normalized_text": "EVP",
                    "probability": 0.4226,
                    "start": 172,
                    "type": "Organization"
                },
                {
                    "end": 209,
                    "normalized_text": "Olivier Blum",
                    "probability": 0.9658,
                    "start": 198,
                    "type": "Person"
                }
            ],
            "urls": [
                {
                    "display_url": "spr.ly/l/6019u5yI9",
                    "end": 250,
                    "expanded_url": "http://spr.ly/l/6019u5yI9",
                    "start": 227,
                    "status": 200,
                    "unwound_url": "http://spr.ly/l/6019u5yI9",
                    "url": "https://t.co/Oee74qtF13"
                },
                {
                    "display_url": "pic.twitter.com/aW5ZAiw63o",
                    "end": 274,
                    "expanded_url": "https://twitter.com/SchneiderElec/status/1717186761242337787/photo/1",
                    "media_key": "3_1717186755936309249",
                    "start": 251,
                    "url": "https://t.co/aW5ZAiw63o"
                }
            ]
        },
        "id": "1717186761242337787",
        "lang": "en",
        "public_metrics": {
            "bookmark_count": 0,
            "impression_count": 1172,
            "like_count": 10,
            "quote_count": 0,
            "reply_count": 0,
            "retweet_count": 5
        },
        "text": "Asia is feeling the brunt of ClimateChange, with India, China, and Singapore all experiencing extreme heat waves in recent months. \nIn his new article for Nikkei Asia, our EVP for Energy Management Olivier Blum explores (cont) https://t.co/Oee74qtF13 https://t.co/aW5ZAiw63o"
    }
}