{
    "1241220741649047552": {
        "author_id": "1112667704010436609",
        "created_at": "2020-03-21T04:31:00.000Z",
        "edit_history_tweet_ids": [
            "1241220741649047552"
        ],
        "entities": {
            "annotations": [
                {
                    "end": 4,
                    "normalized_text": "EDPR",
                    "probability": 0.4292,
                    "start": 1,
                    "type": "Organization"
                },
                {
                    "end": 42,
                    "normalized_text": "Oklahoma",
                    "probability": 0.9751,
                    "start": 35,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 70,
                    "normalized_text": "Murray",
                    "probability": 0.8077,
                    "start": 65,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 78,
                    "normalized_text": "Carter",
                    "probability": 0.7974,
                    "start": 73,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 85,
                    "normalized_text": "Grady",
                    "probability": 0.8144,
                    "start": 81,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 92,
                    "normalized_text": "Caddo",
                    "probability": 0.7689,
                    "start": 88,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 102,
                    "normalized_text": "Comanche",
                    "probability": 0.78,
                    "start": 95,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 113,
                    "normalized_text": "Kiowa",
                    "probability": 0.7789,
                    "start": 109,
                    "type": "Place"
                }
            ],
            "hashtags": [
                {
                    "end": 5,
                    "start": 0,
                    "tag": "EDPR"
                }
            ],
            "urls": [
                {
                    "display_url": "okenergytoday.com/2020/03/a-stro…",
                    "end": 148,
                    "expanded_url": "http://www.okenergytoday.com/2020/03/a-strong-year-for-wind/",
                    "start": 125,
                    "url": "https://t.co/zZEQHqjXri"
                }
            ]
        },
        "id": "1241220741649047552",
        "lang": "en",
        "public_metrics": {
            "bookmark_count": 0,
            "impression_count": 0,
            "like_count": 0,
            "quote_count": 0,
            "reply_count": 0,
            "retweet_count": 0
        },
        "text": "#EDPR operates more than 620 MW in Oklahoma at our wind farms in Murray, Carter, Grady, Caddo, Comanche, and Kiowa counties. https://t.co/zZEQHqjXri"
    }
}