{
    "1247526586154287104": {
        "author_id": "1112667704010436609",
        "created_at": "2020-04-07T14:08:10.000Z",
        "edit_history_tweet_ids": [
            "1247526586154287104"
        ],
        "entities": {
            "annotations": [
                {
                    "end": 4,
                    "normalized_text": "EDPR",
                    "probability": 0.6077,
                    "start": 1,
                    "type": "Organization"
                },
                {
                    "end": 46,
                    "normalized_text": "coronavirus",
                    "probability": 0.9345,
                    "start": 36,
                    "type": "Other"
                },
                {
                    "end": 116,
                    "normalized_text": "Belgium",
                    "probability": 0.9482,
                    "start": 110,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 124,
                    "normalized_text": "Brazil",
                    "probability": 0.9585,
                    "start": 119,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 134,
                    "normalized_text": "Colombia",
                    "probability": 0.976,
                    "start": 127,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 141,
                    "normalized_text": "Spain",
                    "probability": 0.9473,
                    "start": 137,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 146,
                    "normalized_text": "USA",
                    "probability": 0.9718,
                    "start": 144,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 154,
                    "normalized_text": "France",
                    "probability": 0.9652,
                    "start": 149,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 162,
                    "normalized_text": "Greece",
                    "probability": 0.9707,
                    "start": 157,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 169,
                    "normalized_text": "Italy",
                    "probability": 0.9451,
                    "start": 165,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 177,
                    "normalized_text": "Poland",
                    "probability": 0.9283,
                    "start": 172,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 191,
                    "normalized_text": "Romania",
                    "probability": 0.9894,
                    "start": 185,
                    "type": "Place"
                }
            ],
            "hashtags": [
                {
                    "end": 5,
                    "start": 0,
                    "tag": "EDPR"
                },
                {
                    "end": 47,
                    "start": 35,
                    "tag": "coronavirus"
                }
            ],
            "urls": [
                {
                    "display_url": "edpr.com/en/news/2020/0…",
                    "end": 283,
                    "expanded_url": "https://www.edpr.com/en/news/2020/04/07/edpr-will-contribute-eu750000-fight-against-covid-19",
                    "start": 260,
                    "status": 200,
                    "unwound_url": "https://www.edpr.com/en/news/edpr-will-contribute-eu750000-fight-against-covid-19",
                    "url": "https://t.co/doN6RAbJ27"
                }
            ]
        },
        "id": "1247526586154287104",
        "lang": "en",
        "public_metrics": {
            "bookmark_count": 0,
            "impression_count": 0,
            "like_count": 8,
            "quote_count": 1,
            "reply_count": 0,
            "retweet_count": 3
        },
        "text": "#EDPR contributes to fight against #coronavirus donating €750k to initiatives protecting local communities in Belgium, Brazil, Colombia, Spain, USA, France, Greece, Italy, Poland &amp; Romania, where our main activities are based. Together we can defeat this! https://t.co/doN6RAbJ27"
    }
}