{
    "1293976916450578435": {
        "author_id": "1112667704010436609",
        "created_at": "2020-08-13T18:25:12.000Z",
        "edit_history_tweet_ids": [
            "1293976916450578435"
        ],
        "entities": {
            "annotations": [
                {
                    "end": 4,
                    "normalized_text": "EDPR",
                    "probability": 0.3996,
                    "start": 1,
                    "type": "Organization"
                },
                {
                    "end": 38,
                    "normalized_text": "AmericanWindWeek",
                    "probability": 0.6752,
                    "start": 23,
                    "type": "Other"
                },
                {
                    "end": 98,
                    "normalized_text": "Chalmers",
                    "probability": 0.4636,
                    "start": 91,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 109,
                    "normalized_text": "Brookston",
                    "probability": 0.8985,
                    "start": 101,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 119,
                    "normalized_text": "Reynolds",
                    "probability": 0.6748,
                    "start": 112,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 132,
                    "normalized_text": "Wolcott",
                    "probability": 0.6143,
                    "start": 126,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 175,
                    "normalized_text": "Lake Wind Farm",
                    "probability": 0.5341,
                    "start": 162,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 194,
                    "normalized_text": "White County",
                    "probability": 0.6726,
                    "start": 183,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 203,
                    "normalized_text": "Indiana",
                    "probability": 0.8894,
                    "start": 197,
                    "type": "Place"
                }
            ],
            "hashtags": [
                {
                    "end": 5,
                    "start": 0,
                    "tag": "EDPR"
                },
                {
                    "end": 39,
                    "start": 22,
                    "tag": "AmericanWindWeek"
                },
                {
                    "end": 229,
                    "start": 209,
                    "tag": "WindBuildsTheFuture"
                }
            ],
            "urls": [
                {
                    "display_url": "globenewswire.com/news-release/2…",
                    "end": 254,
                    "expanded_url": "https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2020/08/13/2078066/0/en/EDP-Renewables-provides-300k-support-package-to-communities-surrounding-Meadow-Lake-Wind-Farm.html",
                    "start": 231,
                    "status": 200,
                    "unwound_url": "https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2020/08/13/2078066/0/en/EDP-Renewables-provides-300k-support-package-to-communities-surrounding-Meadow-Lake-Wind-Farm.html",
                    "url": "https://t.co/HHSvi4bNuP"
                }
            ]
        },
        "id": "1293976916450578435",
        "lang": "en",
        "public_metrics": {
            "bookmark_count": 0,
            "impression_count": 0,
            "like_count": 4,
            "quote_count": 1,
            "reply_count": 0,
            "retweet_count": 0
        },
        "text": "#EDPR is rounding out #AmericanWindWeek by announcing a $300,000 commitment to support the Chalmers, Brookston, Reynolds, and Wolcott communities near our Meadow Lake Wind Farm on in White County, Indiana!  \n\n#WindBuildsTheFuture  https://t.co/HHSvi4bNuP"
    }
}