{
    "1338493903645925376": {
        "author_id": "1112667704010436609",
        "created_at": "2020-12-14T14:39:49.000Z",
        "edit_history_tweet_ids": [
            "1338493903645925376"
        ],
        "entities": {
            "annotations": [
                {
                    "end": 16,
                    "normalized_text": "Americas",
                    "probability": 0.821,
                    "start": 9,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 23,
                    "normalized_text": "EDPR",
                    "probability": 0.44,
                    "start": 20,
                    "type": "Organization"
                },
                {
                    "end": 71,
                    "normalized_text": "Brazil",
                    "probability": 0.9366,
                    "start": 66,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 74,
                    "normalized_text": "🇧🇷",
                    "probability": 0.5159,
                    "start": 73,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 84,
                    "normalized_text": "Colombia",
                    "probability": 0.9553,
                    "start": 77,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 87,
                    "normalized_text": "🇨🇴",
                    "probability": 0.5978,
                    "start": 86,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 95,
                    "normalized_text": "Mexico",
                    "probability": 0.8723,
                    "start": 90,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 98,
                    "normalized_text": "🇲🇽",
                    "probability": 0.4949,
                    "start": 97,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 106,
                    "normalized_text": "Canada",
                    "probability": 0.9307,
                    "start": 101,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 121,
                    "normalized_text": "US",
                    "probability": 0.8966,
                    "start": 120,
                    "type": "Place"
                }
            ],
            "hashtags": [
                {
                    "end": 24,
                    "start": 19,
                    "tag": "EDPR"
                }
            ]
        },
        "id": "1338493903645925376",
        "lang": "en",
        "public_metrics": {
            "bookmark_count": 0,
            "impression_count": 0,
            "like_count": 0,
            "quote_count": 0,
            "reply_count": 0,
            "retweet_count": 0
        },
        "text": "🌎 In the Americas, #EDPR contribution will go to those in need in Brazil 🇧🇷, Colombia 🇨🇴, Mexico 🇲🇽, Canada 🇨🇦, and the US 🇺🇸."
    }
}