{
    "1338484138375049220": {
        "author_id": "1112667704010436609",
        "created_at": "2020-12-14T14:01:01.000Z",
        "edit_history_tweet_ids": [
            "1338484138375049220"
        ],
        "entities": {
            "annotations": [
                {
                    "end": 10,
                    "normalized_text": "Europe",
                    "probability": 0.9215,
                    "start": 5,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 52,
                    "normalized_text": "EDPR",
                    "probability": 0.3844,
                    "start": 49,
                    "type": "Organization"
                },
                {
                    "end": 90,
                    "normalized_text": "Spain",
                    "probability": 0.9067,
                    "start": 86,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 103,
                    "normalized_text": "Portugal",
                    "probability": 0.9142,
                    "start": 96,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 106,
                    "normalized_text": "🇵🇹",
                    "probability": 0.5118,
                    "start": 105,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 114,
                    "normalized_text": "Greece",
                    "probability": 0.9353,
                    "start": 109,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 117,
                    "normalized_text": "🇬🇷",
                    "probability": 0.5582,
                    "start": 116,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 124,
                    "normalized_text": "Italy",
                    "probability": 0.8777,
                    "start": 120,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 127,
                    "normalized_text": "🇮🇹",
                    "probability": 0.647,
                    "start": 126,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 135,
                    "normalized_text": "France",
                    "probability": 0.8899,
                    "start": 130,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 146,
                    "normalized_text": "Poland",
                    "probability": 0.8711,
                    "start": 141,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 162,
                    "normalized_text": "Romania",
                    "probability": 0.9471,
                    "start": 156,
                    "type": "Place"
                }
            ],
            "hashtags": [
                {
                    "end": 53,
                    "start": 48,
                    "tag": "EDPR"
                }
            ],
            "mentions": [
                {
                    "end": 31,
                    "id": "796760508468723712",
                    "start": 17,
                    "username": "EuroFoodBanks"
                }
            ]
        },
        "id": "1338484138375049220",
        "lang": "en",
        "public_metrics": {
            "bookmark_count": 0,
            "impression_count": 0,
            "like_count": 0,
            "quote_count": 0,
            "reply_count": 1,
            "retweet_count": 1
        },
        "text": "🌍 In Europe, the @EuroFoodBanks will distribute #EDPR aid through local food banks in Spain 🇪🇸, Portugal 🇵🇹, Greece 🇬🇷, Italy 🇮🇹, France 🇫🇷, Poland 🇵🇱, and Romania 🇷🇴."
    }
}