{
    "1319259798345551872": {
        "author_id": "606342802",
        "created_at": "2020-10-22T12:50:21.000Z",
        "edit_history_tweet_ids": [
            "1319259798345551872"
        ],
        "entities": {
            "annotations": [
                {
                    "end": 7,
                    "normalized_text": "Oman",
                    "probability": 0.4124,
                    "start": 4,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 13,
                    "normalized_text": "IKEA",
                    "probability": 0.5522,
                    "start": 10,
                    "type": "Organization"
                },
                {
                    "end": 31,
                    "normalized_text": "Oman",
                    "probability": 0.9529,
                    "start": 28,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 37,
                    "normalized_text": "IKEA",
                    "probability": 0.5142,
                    "start": 34,
                    "type": "Organization"
                },
                {
                    "end": 59,
                    "normalized_text": "Al-Futtaim",
                    "probability": 0.4496,
                    "start": 50,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 82,
                    "normalized_text": "IKEA",
                    "probability": 0.6373,
                    "start": 79,
                    "type": "Organization"
                },
                {
                    "end": 108,
                    "normalized_text": "of",
                    "probability": 0.4092,
                    "start": 107,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 113,
                    "normalized_text": "Oman",
                    "probability": 0.5404,
                    "start": 110,
                    "type": "Place"
                }
            ],
            "urls": [
                {
                    "display_url": "linkedin.com/posts/vinod-ja…",
                    "end": 184,
                    "expanded_url": "https://www.linkedin.com/posts/vinod-jayan-1aaaab16_ikea-alfuttaim-retail-activity-6724204711202852866-wumQ/",
                    "start": 161,
                    "status": 200,
                    "unwound_url": "https://www.linkedin.com/posts/vinod-jayan-1aaaab16_ikea-alfuttaim-retail-activity-6724204711202852866-wumQ/",
                    "url": "https://t.co/KhphPF3wox"
                }
            ]
        },
        "id": "1319259798345551872",
        "lang": "en",
        "public_metrics": {
            "bookmark_count": 0,
            "impression_count": 0,
            "like_count": 7,
            "quote_count": 0,
            "reply_count": 0,
            "retweet_count": 0
        },
        "text": "Hej Oman! IKEA is coming to Oman. IKEA franchisee Al-Futtaim announced that an IKEA store in the Sultanate of Oman will be opening in the first quarter of 2022. https://t.co/KhphPF3wox"
    }
}