{
    "1671090541054885892": {
        "attachments": {
            "media_keys": [
                "7_1671090184887123968"
            ]
        },
        "author_id": "606342802",
        "created_at": "2023-06-20T09:40:07.000Z",
        "edit_history_tweet_ids": [
            "1671090541054885892"
        ],
        "entities": {
            "annotations": [
                {
                    "end": 110,
                    "normalized_text": "Zahra",
                    "probability": 0.535,
                    "start": 106,
                    "type": "Person"
                },
                {
                    "end": 120,
                    "normalized_text": "Tarek",
                    "probability": 0.559,
                    "start": 116,
                    "type": "Person"
                },
                {
                    "end": 131,
                    "normalized_text": "Syria",
                    "probability": 0.9538,
                    "start": 127,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 141,
                    "normalized_text": "Nataliia",
                    "probability": 0.3932,
                    "start": 134,
                    "type": "Other"
                },
                {
                    "end": 155,
                    "normalized_text": "Yevheniia",
                    "probability": 0.4534,
                    "start": 147,
                    "type": "Other"
                },
                {
                    "end": 168,
                    "normalized_text": "Ukraine",
                    "probability": 0.9448,
                    "start": 162,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 175,
                    "normalized_text": "Edgar",
                    "probability": 0.4754,
                    "start": 171,
                    "type": "Person"
                },
                {
                    "end": 190,
                    "normalized_text": "Venezuela",
                    "probability": 0.9595,
                    "start": 182,
                    "type": "Place"
                },
                {
                    "end": 202,
                    "normalized_text": "Hassan",
                    "probability": 0.5687,
                    "start": 197,
                    "type": "Person"
                },
                {
                    "end": 213,
                    "normalized_text": "Sudan",
                    "probability": 0.9314,
                    "start": 209,
                    "type": "Place"
                }
            ],
            "hashtags": [
                {
                    "end": 263,
                    "start": 240,
                    "tag": "takingbackthenarrative"
                },
                {
                    "end": 280,
                    "start": 264,
                    "tag": "worldrefugeeday"
                }
            ],
            "urls": [
                {
                    "display_url": "ikea.com/gb/en/this-is-…",
                    "end": 239,
                    "expanded_url": "https://www.ikea.com/gb/en/this-is-ikea/community-engagement/changing-the-narrative-on-refugees/",
                    "start": 216,
                    "status": 200,
                    "unwound_url": "https://www.ikea.com/gb/en/this-is-ikea/community-engagement/changing-the-narrative-on-refugees/",
                    "url": "https://t.co/A4gcByrdAB"
                },
                {
                    "display_url": "pic.twitter.com/TR7pd7Msol",
                    "end": 304,
                    "expanded_url": "https://twitter.com/IKEA/status/1671090541054885892/video/1",
                    "media_key": "7_1671090184887123968",
                    "start": 281,
                    "url": "https://t.co/TR7pd7Msol"
                }
            ]
        },
        "id": "1671090541054885892",
        "lang": "en",
        "public_metrics": {
            "bookmark_count": 0,
            "impression_count": 17707,
            "like_count": 21,
            "quote_count": 2,
            "reply_count": 22,
            "retweet_count": 4
        },
        "text": "It’s time to hear the less spoken side of refugees, time to dispel the myths and discover the truth. Meet Zahra and Tarek from Syria, Nataliia and Yevheniia from Ukraine, Edgar from Venezuela, and Hassan from Sudan. https://t.co/A4gcByrdAB #takingbackthenarrative #worldrefugeeday https://t.co/TR7pd7Msol"
    }
}